<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Daniel/Desktop/dd_class_mod/git_mods/my_mods/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Gourmet Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>unlisted</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>New Hero</Tags>
		<Tags>Pig</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[img]https://i.imgur.com/IL0GnEC.png[/img]

	[h1]Overview[/h1]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	[i]&quot;A refined taste elevates us from the beasts. Hunger drags us down beneath them.&quot;[/i]

	An unlikely individual has trotted its way into town and made itself at home within the tavern&apos;s kitchen. While its monstrous visage and mannerisms have made the locals more than uneasy, it has not yet shown to be overtly hostile, and what&apos;s more it has proven to be an astonishingly skilled chef. The townsfolk have decided to let sleeping dogs lie as it were and allow for the continued existence of this pig man so long as it remains well behaved and provides more delicious meals. You may even be able to turn the beast&apos;s innate ferocity onto the more looming threats the Hamlet faces with enough persuasion... and treats.

	The Gourmet is a front-line behemoth that can dish out as much punishment as it receives. Equipped with debilitating attacks that weaken foes, he can set up big payoffs for either himself or his allies to capitalize on. He is able fulfill the role of a tanky support protecting the team from harm or as a potent finisher with heavy blows.

	[h2]Combat Skills[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/Ty7AOwT.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/JEm9ooN.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/ws3QpYM.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/6hUAlVL.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/l2mHlyZ.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/tV5K1lk.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/4rK4oZ0.png[/img]

	[h2]Camping Skills[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/PaxnQ8T.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/1P8VwzP.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/rotgqK1.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/uZXD2Gw.png[/img]

	[h2]Unique Food Supplies[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	While on a team during expiditions, the Gourmet puts its culinary skills to work both on and off the battlefield. You may discover that they have created a well prepared meal made from ingredients in the local environment. Those who are willing to partake in these treats may find themselves bolstered for the coming battles. Be wary however, for a swine&apos;s diet may not be agreeable with others, especially for one as gastronomicaly adventurous as this...

	You have a chance of finding unique food items after a battle or by using the &apos;Leftovers&apos; camping skill. There are two unique items to each region along with two additional generic items that can be found. Each one provides different benefits such as buffs, heals, and resistances but they also come with a cost to said conditions. 
	
	The in game descriptions are intentionally vague hinting at what you can possibly expect to invite some risk and discovery. For those wishing to have a detailed explanation of the effects in order to strategize, a document going over all of the items and their associated effects can be found in the following link.

	[url=https://docs.google.com/document/d/11PBxBgjS9Ko6oyGClcMLiEFrsDoNEijry4-R2N7a-cA/edit]Gourmet Food Items Google Doc[/url]

	[h2]Trinkets[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/NID91l7.png[/img]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/nA50G0O.png[/img]

	[h2]Additional Info[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	[list]
		[*]The Gourmet is not Religious
		[*]When landing a crit the Gourmet gains a small hp regen
		[*]The Gourmet will refuse to party with other Gourmets
		[*]Belongs to the Outsider&apos;s Bonfire District
		[*]Canon name is Napoleon
	[/list]

	[b]Potential Content to be Added Later Maybe[/b]
	[list]
		[*]Town Events
		[*]More Color Palettes
		[*]Vermintide food items, trinkets, and custom barks
		[*]And more???
	[/list]

	[h2]Localization[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	While this mod should be usable in every language, it does not have any translations other than English. If you would like to assist in translating, please contact me either on Steam or Discord
	
	[h2]Credits and Such[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	Character art, concept, code, and dang near everything made by me. Darkest Dungeon is a favorite game of mine and having developed new skills over the years wanting to create things for others to enjoy, I decided it was high time to contribute to the community with this first (arguably too ambitious) mod. Many thanks for checking this out and let me know what yall think. Hopefully more content will follow this and hopefully won&apos;t take me nearly as long to complete.

	Special thanks to:

	[b]OxTailSafu[/b] - playtesting and feedback
	[b]Bulletbombat[/b] - playtesting and feedback
	[b]Vintage[/b] - playtesting and feedback
	[b]Zahara[/b] - playtesting and feedback
	[b]Zalgo[/b] - playtesting and feedback
	[b]Cerebralcloud92[/b] - playtesting, feedback, and coding assistance
	[b]Sherin[/b] - coding and general modding assistance
	[b]Sasiji[/b] - for being the go to Code Helper for myself and the modding community
	[b]TheAwkwardHeady[/b] - feedback and general modding assistance
	[b]Slightly_Seal[/b] - for allowing me to sample one of their sprites to use in the target fx for &apos;Devour&apos;
	[b]TiltedHat[/b] - assistance with art programs such as Krita and DragonBones

	And finally thanks to everyone on the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fdarkestdungeon]Official Darkest Dungeon Discord Server[/url]. Thanks for all the feedback and assistance and for being so welcoming into the community. 

	[h2]Disclaimer[/h2]
	[h2]----------------------------------------------------[/h2]
	&apos;The Gourmet Class Mod&apos; is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>2960108084</PublishedFileId>
</project>

